maphill.com 2014-06-29

# Privacy Policy | Maphill

This privacy policy is here for you to understand what information we may collect while operating Maphill website. By using this website, you agree to the collection and use of your information by us in accordance with this privacy policy.

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, we collect non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Our purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how our visitors use our website. From time to time, we may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of our website.

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

We do not collect any Personally Identifying Information about you unless you voluntarily provide such information, such as when you contact us. If you send us an email, we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help other users. We take all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. We may use cookies to help us identify and track visitors, their usage of our website, and their preferences. Visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using our website, with the drawback that certain features of our website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

## Ads

Ads appearing on our website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by us only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, we may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, and in our sole discretion. We encourage visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
